Then you would have been on a job trip in Madeira and bought with you candy home.
Yes.
Since we moved here, we have noticed that it was not typically Portuguese candy.
- No.
- So today we will offer what is typical of Portugal.
- Yes.
- Or, we should be offered it.
We'll test it, simply.
- Yeah!
Should we start?
- Yes I think so!
"Flocos de neve"
There are candies in red paper, and they are white.
"Flocos de neve" means "snowflakes".
No, Laura.
You must not eat it.
Not yet.
- Laura sits with a small apple piece while we test sweets.
- Yes.
- Are you ready?
Let's go.
- It's good.
- mm, that's it.
... so it is because the sun is going down and we try to set the light so it will match all the time.
But it can make the light jump a little now and then.
Hope you stand out with it.
Sorry for that.
"Regina's chocolate umbrellas"
This is what it looks like inside the paper.
In Portugal it doesn't seem to rain that much.
This is their definition of umbrellas.
- Shall we drive?
- Yes.
- I still have my other candy.
- huh?!
- (Axel) Do you have the other one?
- Here.
- But me ... - Well!
It's the crazy corner over there.
I don't know what they are doing.
I've already tasted.
- 0 of 0. - I also give 0.
“Pipocas Doces”
So it's cute popcorn.
(Axel) Oh, what cute.
- Pretty good.
- Nah-ä.
- I prefer salty popcorn.
- Me too.
- I've never taken this.
- Cute popcorn?
Nah.
I've taken it.
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
I give 3 out of 5.
I give 1.8 out of 5.
- I had to ... - it's very ... Likörig.
- A lot of liquor.
- It just really ran out.
Yes.
And so it's like a cherry inside, with some chewing resistance ..
This one was probably one of the worst we have ever tested, I think.
It is non -alcoholic.
(Alma and Harry Frustar and Milling)
- What is this?
- So, that one was so disgusting and strong.
- Yes, so ... - Who wants to eat this?
May I only say one thing?
It feels like you have to have the worst leather tongue to think this is wonderful to eat.
It's like drinking hand spirit.
No, Fy!
It was so disgusting.
- I give noool ... - I also give zero.
- So it got some points, at least?
- A little.
I give this 0 points.
Nothing for me.
I give 1 point because it was sugar free.
It gets a small bonus because of it.
- ♪ Zero, zero, zero, zero!
♪ - ♪ zero, zero, zero, zero!
♪
Ouch.
♪ Alma's face is like a zero!
Check out her feud!
♪
♪ And her eye is like a zero!
And pipitas, and dad and middle and mom!
Everything is like a zero!
♪
Help!
- Oh my God.
- I don't know what's going on here now.
"Dr. Bentes Peitoral"
These are hard candies.